继   承   之   战
第 4 季  第 1 集
你好  -您好啊 很高兴见到您
Hey! -Hi, how are you? Good to see you.
他来了
Here he is.
看起来状态不错啊
Looks good in there, huh?
老爸 生日快乐
Happy birthday, Pa!
我们继续吧 把这些算作否决方案
Let's move on and put this in the " No" Pile.
能告诉我 你关于这套的想法吗
Can you tell me your idea with this one?
方便我理解 这款品牌形象设计方案 背后的理念
Just so I know what the thinking was behind this branding
小罗
Romey!
你在哪呢 老弟
Where are you. Dude?
是我哥哥 他来了
It's my brother. He's coming
先标记一下这套 继续看下一套吧
Let's put a pin in this one and move on.
让一千朵向日葵绽放吧[百花齐放] 小罗
Let a thousand sunflowers bloom, Romey
我要和你共同创业 老弟
I wanna start a business with you. Brother.
最近怎样 阿泰  -这套不行 过
-'Sup, T? -This is nothing. No.
对吗 糟透了  -大家好啊 进行的怎么样了
Right, fuck chops? -Hey, guys! How are we looking?
我们觉得这一套 可以运用在每个纵向的…
This is one that we feel could work across every vertical…
-不  -这绝对不行
-No. -That's a hard no.
就我们希望这个新项目“百家”呈现的形象而言
In terms of what we need for our new venture, The Hundred
-这  -这糟透了
-They're... They're shitty.
太糟了 我们可以直说吧
They're shitty. We can just be honest here, right?
百家是“订阅堆栈“[美版公众号]和"大师课”[在线教育平台]
The Hundred is Sub stack meets Masterclass
经济学人 以及 纽约客 的组合
meets The Economist meets The New Yorker.
我记得咱们说好要“标志性”
I feel like we said " Iconic "
可你们却走向了“讽刺性”
and you guys are leaning " Ironic "
阿泰 投资人好像来了
Hey, T? I think the money is here
小罗 你的安保对他们的态度很奇怪
Rome, I think your security are being very weird with them.
他们看着蠢蠢的 可能还有点种族歧视
They seem stupid and probably racist.
你看起来好疲惫 你的脸让我头疼
Well, you look tired, and your face is giving me a headache.
谢谢你  -你去哪了 老妹
-Thank you. -So, where have you been, sis?
什么意思 贴贴
What do you mean? Hey!
所以 你去哪了
Where have you been?
堵车 接电话 谈生意 谈这个
It was traffic. And a call. Business. For this
朋友们 你们的反馈很好
Guys, this is good feedback.
我们再重新选一遍
We're gonna circle back on
等下和你们聊
exactly all that stuff and we'll talk soon
回见了
See you later.
因为堵车吗
So, traffic? Huh?
对啊 堵车 怎么了
Yeah, traffic. What?
小西 你在捣鬼吗
Shivy, are you snaking?
我们听说 你一直在和希门尼斯交接班子联系
We hear that you've been talking to the Jimenez transition team.
-没有啊  -没有吗
-Well, no. -No?
没有
No.
那我们的朋友说的是假话了吗
So it's lies that our friend told us?
他们在对我们撒谎吗
They're lying to us?
我是和他们谈过 但那是因为我在帮他们忙
I've talked to them, but it's because I'm helping them out
你们已经知道了
as you already know.
那你们是在联系呗
So you are talking?
没有
No.
我回了通电话 他们就想聊聊
I returned a call. They wanna talk about talking.
他们想聊聊吗
They wanna talk about talking?
怎么了 拜托
What? Come on.
他们还没赢下选举 可能不会赢
They haven't won the election, and they might not
爸可能不会卖公司
and Dad might not sell,
你们俩有可能跑路
and you two might bail
这是个可能性很多的情况
and it's a may be, may be, may be situation
爸一定会卖掉公司
Dad is obviously selling
我们正他妈在选新商标呢
We're looking at fucking logos here.
我还草拟了一份从韦斯达退出的辞呈
I drafted a resignation statement from Waystar
我也一样
Yeah, same.
只是 这是很重大的一步 我们不能有些备选方案吗
This is just a big step, and so, can't we keep some options?
还备选方案呢 还有两天爸就要把公司卖掉了
Keep options open? We're two days out from Dad selling
你必须要理解一件事
Here's what you have to understand
我是吸过海洛因的人
I've smoked horse
他害怕针头 他不是真正的瘾君子
He's scared of needle s. He's not a real junkie
我的生活需要这些 让人上瘾的东西
I need something super fucking absorbing in my life
所以 如果这个行不通 可以直接告诉我吗
And if it isn't gonna be this, please just let me know, right?
因为 我累死累活 全国各地到处飞
I feel like I've been flying around the country
和大人物们面对面 进行严肃的对话
having serious fucking conversations with serious people,
挥霍我的个人资产
expending serious personal capital
然后 搞一些厉害的人物 进董事会
and getting big fucking names on board.
一样啊 我也是 那我们都在这么做
-Same. Me, too. -So we've all been doing that.
你在担心现在的规模太小吗
Are you worried that this is may be too small scale?
什么 不会 没有 你觉得呢
What? No. No, do you?
我吗 当然没有
Me? No
我对“百家“唯一的担心只有 是不是太美好了点
My only worry with The Hundred is it literally too good?
比如 为什么还没人做过这些呢
Like, why hasn't anyone done this before?
我加入
I am in.
我加入 真的
I'm in. I am.
好的
Okay.
祝你生日快乐
Happy birthday to you!
祝你生日快乐 亲爱的洛根
Happy birthday, dear Logan!
祝你生日快乐
Happy birthday to you!
真是要了命了
Jesus fucking Christ!
你还好吗 洛哥
You okay, Loge?
奇怪的一家! 这奇怪的一家人
Munsters. Meet the fucking Munsters
这他妈又是谁
Who the fuck is this now?
我猜 我们应该... 你好 欢迎
-So, I guess we should... -Hi! Welcome!
欢迎 格雷格和…  -这是布丽奇特
Welcome, Greg and... -This is Bridget.
布丽奇特 这是凯莉 洛根的…
Bridget, this is Kerry. Logan's.
朋友 助手 和顾问
Friend, assistant, and advisor.
你好 我是布丽奇特  -你好 布丽奇特 很高兴认识你
Hey, I'm Bridget. -Hi, Bridget. So great to meet you.
格雷格 我和你去帮布丽奇特拿点喝的吧
Greg, let me and you grab Bridget a drink
好的 那先失陪了 布丽奇特
Okay. So, excuse us, Bridget
抱歉 我们很快回来
I'm sorry. We'll be right back
不要拘束
Make yourself at home.
她是哪位 格雷格,  -这是我的女伴
Who is this, Greg? -That's my date
没错 可她是谁
Right, but who is she?
我带了位女伴来 没问题吧
I brought a date. That's okay, right?
她叫什么 她的全名
What's her name? What's her full name?
是随机的炮友吗 布丽奇特·随机炮友
Is it Random-fuck? Bridget Random-fuck?
她是在软件上认识的吗 格雷格
Is she from the apps, Greg?
我真的喜欢她 我可能爱上她了
I really like her. I might have fallen for her.
好棒啊 你之前有多少位女伴呢
That's great. How many previous dates have you had?
凯莉 我不太确定你的问题是否合适
Kerry, I'm not sure this is appropriate
我们这儿不是他妈的汉堡店 格雷格
We're not a fucking Shake Shack, Greg
这不是约炮前的派对 这是生日派对
This isn't a pre-fuck party. It's a birthday party
我是表亲 我可以带一位来的
I am a cousin. I get a plus one
我就像是荣誉小孩
I'm like an honorary kid
你是荣誉小孩吗  -当然是了
You're an honorary kid? --Yeah
玛西娅说过…  -玛西娅不在这
-Marcia once said... -Marcia's not here.
她在米兰购物 永远不会回来了
She's in Milan, shopping. Forever.
你应该知道
You do know that
我们正处于一场竞争激烈的竞选中
we're in the middle of a hotly-contested election,
你叔公马上要进行一笔特大型交易
your uncle is on the brink of a very large sale
同时还在打量一笔很敏感的收购
and scoping out a very sensitive acquisition?
你怎么能确定
Are you certain that she's not
她不是打算在董事会前打探消息呢
gonna leak details right before the board meeting?
你确定她不是敌对公司的线人吗
Do you know she's not a hostile corporate asset?
是这样 我们正在寻找
Okay. So, we're looking for investment partners
一项革命性 新媒体品牌的 投资伙伴
for a revolutionary, new media brand
这个品牌 会重新定义 二十一世纪的新闻
that's gonna redefine news for the 21st century
它是一个 必不可少的 定制信息中心
It's an indispensable, bespoke information hub.
百家 最好的专家 最棒的作者
" The Hundred, greatest experts, best writers,"
每个领域的最强大脑 从巴以冲突到人工智能
" Top minds in every field, from Israel-Palestine to A I "
到米其林餐厅
To Michelin restaurants.
一站式信息处 高能量信息餐
One-stop info shop, high-calorie info snacks "
抱歉 我接下电话
Sorry. I'm gonna take this
好吧 接吧
All right, take it.
-你好  -你好啊
-Hello? -Hey. How are you?
挺好的 你好吗 怎么了
Good. How are you? What is it?
我打来 就是想早早给你说一声
I was just calling to give you a heads up
打声招呼
and just to say hi
然后 让你知道昨晚我和内奥米·皮尔斯
and just to let you know that I just had a little drink
喝了点小酒
with Naomi Pierce last night
以防万一 我只是想向你告知一下
Just in case of anything, I just wanted to inform you
抱歉 你在告知我吗
I'm sorry, you're informing me?
我只是出于尊重 提出请求
I just wanted to perform the ask out of due deference
以防狗仔泄露照片 或者被议论到
just in case of photos or getting talked about
抱歉 你是在请求 还是在告知我
I'm sorry, you're asking me or you're informing me?
小西 这不是什么大事
Shiv, it's not a thing.
那为什么要让我知道
Then why are you letting me know?
因为这不是生意 可这是…
Because it's not business. But it is..
没关系 你在和我哥的前任约会
It's fine. You're dating my brother's ex.
完全 OK
It's fine.
小西 不是的 只是社交
Shiv, no. It's social.
跟裤裆没关系
It's not a sexual thing.
所以 没什么需要跟你说的
So there's nothing I need to tell you about
但你还是跟我说了
And yet, you're telling me
因为 我碰巧遇到玛琳达了 好吗
Because I bumped into Mar linda, okay?
她那张嘴 什么事都要问
And of course, she got her little beak in.
我没办法了 才骗她 这不是谈生意
so I had to tell her it wasn't business because she asked
所以 重点是 根本没什么需要担心的 明白吗
So, the headline is there's nothing to worry about. Okay?
我知道了 完全没问题
It's fine, it's all fucking fine.
老实说 你请便吧
Seriously. Knock yourself out
我才不会关心 你们俩在小角落 怎么狠狠打桩呢
Go fucking nail her in the coat check. I don't care.
圣保罗小伙 终于登上人生巅峰了
The kid from St. Paul has really made it.
我还以为 根据我们约定好的
I just thought under the term what we agreed
这是需要和你商量的事
this was something worth discussing
根本没必要商量
You don't discuss something.
汤姆 木已成舟 有什么可商量的
Tom, that's already fucking happening
你不会还想着说 “小西你会不会介意” 假如说
You don't say " Shiv, do you mind,"
我正在餐厅和内奥米合体
" Naomi and I are at the Pierre and I'm inside her."
你会介意我内射吗“  -随你便吧
-" Would you mind if I ejaculate?" -Whatever.
随你怎么说 我在日程表上看到
Fine. Hey, look. I saw from the calendar update
你今晚回来 是吧  -对
you're back in the city tonight? -Yeah
所以呢 你为什么要和她见面 发生什么事了
So, why the fuck are you meeting with her? What's going on?
保重 小西
Take care, Shiv.
这就好比 一个给每位用户量身定制的私密俱乐部
It's like a private members'club, but for everyone
有点标题党的味道 只不过针对的是精英阶层
It is click bait in a way, but for smart people.
宗旨是不以盈利为目的
We have the ethos of a non-profit
却能带来巨额的利润 小西 你没事吧
but a path to crazy margins. Shiv, you okay?
-我没事 -你确定吗
-Yeah. -You sure?
没事 我没事
It's fine, I'm fine.
只不过是
It's just, you know.
汤姆和内奥米·皮尔斯见面了
Tom's apparently out with Naomi Pierce.
你知道这件事吗
Did you know about this?
什么 不知道
What? No.
你和她当时到哪个阶段了  -我怎么知道
Where are you at with her? -I don't know.
我现在一头雾水 我跟她没怎么谈过那事
Like carnival of mind fuck. We have n't really talked
很显然 她现在跟汤姆穿一条裤子了
Well, apparently she's fucking Tom now.
我能去叫他们进来吗
Can I go get them?
当然了 我没事 别担心
Yea h. I'm fine. I'm actually fine.
他也没有…
He's not..
只不过是碰个面罢了
It was just a meeting, apparently
没大事 我们继续吧
so it's fine. Let's do this
真的吗 你问问他们 可不可以稍等我们两分钟
Yeah? Do you think they can just give us two?
可以是可以 只是他们刚坐长途航班过来
I mean, it's fine, but they just got off a long flight
叫他们带上石油 美元
Tell'em they can shove their petrodollars
去鼓捣人权记录吧 我们得跟小妹谈谈
up their human rights record. We need to talk to our sister.
他们不会介意的 巴不得呢
They're fine. They love it.
随便哪里找个记者
Just find them a journalist
给他们点点烟 伺候一下
to burn with cigarettes while they wait
小西 他们私会去了吗
Shi v, is it a date?
我怎么知道
I don't know.
很可能不是 但...
It probably isn't, but..
但这是内奥米·皮尔斯
I mean, Naomi Pierce.
难道是爸
Dad?
提爸是什么意思 你有什么想法
With Dad? You think what?
我的团队给我说
I got sent this from my team
有个女的发了照片墙
Apparently Bun Pierce has
她在老爸家 照片里有邦·皮尔斯
been tagged on some girl's In sta at Dad's
-在爸家  -而且是生日会上
-At Dad's? -At the birthday
那好 董事会马上就要召开了
Okay. Well, board meeting imminent.
难道说 他打算让泛美网科独立出去吗
He sells up, but with A TN spun off?
不会吧 他在等着收购皮尔斯
What? He's lining up a Pierce acquisition
好壮大资金体量吗
to add to his little fucking ATM rump?
也许吧  -又或许只是为了搞我们心态
-I guess. -Or it could just be a brain fuck
老爸挑逗我们的神经 耍从前的老计谋
Dad twisting our turnips, playing the old fuck trombone.
故意派汤姆和内来折磨我们
Set Tom and Nay up to just torture us.
派他们俩来折磨我们
Set them up to torture us?
虽然他是个反社会主义者 但不代表他擅长折磨别人
I mean, he's a sociopath, but he wouldn't be a good torturer.
不是说他没有这个胆量
Not'cause he doesn't have the stomach
他只是没那个耐心
he just doesn't have the patience
我打电话问问内
I'm gonna call Nay.
阿泰  -怎么了
Telly? -Yeah?
阿泰 小阿泰 请问
Telly, jelly, belly, one query.
收购皮尔斯的情况如何 比如说 优乐还有伦巴顿
Pierce, PGN. What's the vibes, YOLO, rumba tron?
他们有兴趣吗
Are they in play?
我知道他们一直很乐意报价
I know they're always open to offers
并且很想要以信托为条件
and the sale contingent on the trust is itchy, I believe.
要我把娜比叫过来吗
Should I call Nab by through?
再给我们五分钟 就五分钟
Five more. Please. Just give us five.
好的 明白
Okay, yeah.
没事吧 老康
Hey. You okay, Con?
没事 在看投票结果呢
Yeah. Just polling
截止日期还剩十天  -你现在如何了
Ten days out... -What are you AT Now?
还行 还算稳  -是的 稳在百分之一的支持率
Solid. Still holding. -Yeah, one percent
最后几天才是最惊险的 结果有可能还会波动
It's just the fear is, in these last days... it could get squeezed.
波动下滑吗 还是
Squeezed down?
还能比百分之一少吗 这不已经是最小的数了吗
From one?'Cause that's the lowest number
当然不是 还有小数点呢
No. There's decimals
他们觉得 我可以再积极主动一点
They're saying that I could need to get aggressive
争取更多的媒体平台的曝光
in certain media markets
鉴于目前腹背受敌的处境
because both sides are trying to squeeze my percent
可真不饶人 现在支持率不是全在他们那边吗
That's greedy, knowing they have all the other percents
我知道 但是
I know, but then...
主动出击的代价可不小哟
It gets awfully spendy to get aggressive
代价有多大呢
Like, how much?
差不多一亿吧
Like another hundred mil
一亿吗 我的天哪
One hundred million? Damn!
那你最后能得到什么呢 直接获胜吗
So, what would you get for that? Could you win?
老天 当然不是
Good Lord, no.
不是的 不会有太大的变化
No. That won't move the needle
最好的结果是 可以保持我目前的支持率
The hope is that would maintain my percent
保留了你现有的支持率 那么就可以...
And for your percent you get...?
他能得到话语权
He gets a place in the conversation.
这也挺好的 因为话语权真的很重要
Which is great,'cause conversation's important to be inside of.
但确实花费有点多哦 对吧 小威
But it is kind of a lot. Right, Will?
一亿吗 当然了
A hundred million? Yeah
但是 如果你花了 你还是会很有钱吧
But if you spent it, you'd still be like rich.
对 当然
Sure, yeah.
话虽如此 还是少了一亿
Nevertheless, like, minus a hundred million
谈到与GoJo合作的这个新项目
When it comes to this new venture with GoJo,
如果您能和马特森谈一谈 那么..
and if you talk to Mats son, consider it..
好的 我会考虑的
Right. Thank you.
那么...
So.
情况不错  -我们摆好架势了吗
-Looks good. -We squared away on this?
万事俱备  只欠东风
Got the structure, got the landing zone.
内奥米认为 南已经失去了经营公司的兴趣
Naomi thinks that Nan has lost all interest in business
内部激进派现在咬着他们不放
The left are going after them now.
一群野蛮人 自相残杀
Savages. They eat their own.
表亲们也想收钱跑路
The cousins want out.
所以 我觉得最后抬一手报价也许
So, I think, a last push on price may be..
再稍稍宣染下文化
Little tummy tickle on culture
内奥米飞回去再次确认情况了
And Naomi's flown out to reassure.
结束了 你成功脱身了 洛根
This is it. You landed the plane, Logan
只剩48小时就完事了 恭喜
48 hours and out. Congratulations!
小叛徒们 最近有什么消息吗
Have you heard from the rats?
小西吗 没有
Shiv? No.
好
Good
但我一直在想一件事 先生
One thing has been on my mind though, sir.
是这样的
Yes.
虽然发生了这么多事 但我相信一切都可以迎刃而解
With one thing and another, I'm sure we'll iron it all out
但是 在人生这场艰辛的旅程中
but the rocky, old road of life
我觉得 妻子这部分 一直都特别棘手
and the wife part of that can be a difficult part of it
你也知道的
As you know.
不是对你进行评价啊
Not to comment.
只是 如果可以听听您的意见的话
just to say it would be great to get your take
当然啦 但愿事情不会发展到那一步 但是..
Hopefully, it won't come to that, but..
假如说 到最后 一段感情终究无法破镜重圆的话
In the end, if there is just too much emotional shrapnel.
您这边会有什么样的看法
I wondered what your view would be.
您要是没兴趣的话 也不必理会
Not that you necessarily need to have one,
一段婚姻 假如说我的婚姻 或者说就是我的婚姻
but what would happen were a marriage, such as mine
到最后无法挽回了
even in fact mine.
会发生什么样的事情呢
if that were to falter to the point of failure?
-假如你和小西离婚了  -是的
-If you and Shiv were to bust up? -Right
我和小西已经尝试了一种解决方式
I guess, Shiv and I have had this experiment,
就是试分居
this trial separation
但是不管发生什么 我们之间的关系不会被影响吧
but whatever happens, we'll always be good, right?
我们的关系不会改变
If we're good, we're good.
好的 这样我就放心了
Okay. Well, that's heartening.
谢谢您
That's heartening
您这么说 我很感动
I'm heartened by that. That's great
凯莉 吃的东西呢
Kerry! Where's the grub?
汤姆都发癫了
Tom's going off his nut here.
所以 你俩是觉得 我们该收购皮尔斯 是吧
So, you two are thinking we should be buying Pierce, huh?
我一眼就看出来
Because that's obviously
你们的心思了 这么说吧
what you're thinking, and let me just say.
这他妈可不就是我们的首选吗
that's quite the fucking pivot!
好吧 你是不是在想 那百家怎么办
Right. You may be thinking, " What about The Hundred?"
或许 去他的百家
May be, fuck The Hundred?
去他的百家 小西 你这么想的
Fuck The Hundred, Shiv?
从迪拜回来之后 你对这个点子爱到发狂
After Dubai, you were high as shit on it.
这基本上就是你的点子
It was basically your idea.
我很喜欢这个 真的  -是吗
-I love it. I do. -You do?
对 我们不能两头一起抓吗
Yes, but can't we do both?
两头一起抓
Can't we do both?
好啊 我们一边开发 看高曝光强执行依赖的
Let's launch a high-visibility execution-dependent
颠覆性新闻品牌
disruptor news brand
还一边给一具传统媒体大鳄的尸体
while simultaneously performing CPR on a fucking corpse
做心脏复苏
of a legacy media conglomerate.
要不要问问泰勒斯
Should we ask Tell is?
好 问问泰勒斯吧 看看他是怎么想的
Yes. Let's ask Tellis. I wonder what he's gonna say.
喂 阿泰 你是宁愿
" Hey, Telly. Would you rather
从融资计划中赚五百万
five million in fees from a funding round "
还是从收购计划中赚三千五百万
" Or 35 million from an acquisition?"
我还认为 咱们要专心搞“百家“的
I thought we were going for The Hundred
小而美的新产业 能快速发展
Small, new, fast on our feet
你害怕跟老爸对着干吗  -不是的 肯
-Are you scared of fighting Dad? -No, Ken.
这些都是老黄历了
That's getting fucking old
你在过去三个月里
You spent the last three months
不是一直在拉赞助找投资吗
hunting down contributors, backers, right?
累得心力交瘁  -我没有什么想法
Working your fucking ass off. -I don't have a view.
我只是觉得 这件事值得探讨一下 好吗
All I would say is, maybe it's worth the conversation, all right?
毕竟是我们的强项
It is our wheelhouse.
皮尔斯好比在谷仓里停了20年的古董车
It's a Daimler that's been in the barn for 20 years
把车上的鸡屎清干净真他妈没准儿
Clear the chicken shit off that thing, fucking may be
好吧 但是我们能负担得起吗
Okay. But can we even afford it?
当然 毕竟现在是打对折了
Yeah, I mean, what, it's... it's half now,
也就是说 差不多八九十亿的样子
So that's, like, eight, nine bil.
卖给GoJo之后 我们能分到二三十亿
And after the GoJo sale, we'll have 2-3 bil.
对 这是我们的经费
So, yeah, that's our nut.
如果把我们的名字和现在手头这些精英放在一起
If we partner up with our name with these fucks here.
加上其他有的没的 还有我们的经验
some other pieces of shit, our experience
小西是性感尤物
Shiv the yummy dummy Dem my
我是正义之战里 无畏的斗士
my profile as the fearless fighter of the good fight
你是那个干环事的浪荡子
you as the dirty little fucker pushing the filth buttons.
这就是新一代的罗伊 我们闪亮登场
Yeah, new gen Roys. We have a fucking song to sing
我是觉得 就生意而言
I mean, as a business it's much better
这要比一个 要我们画饼推销的 初创公司 实际的多
than the made-up company of dreams we were ready to pitch
操 你当初那么喜欢百家
Fuck you! You loved it!
我是喜欢这个点子 很赞 就是有点扯
I do. It's very exciting. But it's kind a bullshit.
罗曼 这是事实 我想大干一场
Rome, it is. I wanna do something.
历史性的选举马上就要开始了
We have a seminal election about to happen
这就是我的1933 我要争取话语权
and it's fucking 1933, and I wanna have a say
罗曼 从已经完善的品牌起步
It makes sense, Rome,
建立一个帝国 这是可以做到的
to start an empire with an established brand.
至少先考虑一下吧
At least rule it out.
讨厌鬼来了
Dis gustibus!
我听说 你闹了个大笑话
I hear you've made an enormous faux pas
所有人 都在嘲笑 你约的那个姑娘
and everyone's laughing up their sleeves about your date
啊 为什么啊
What? Why?
还为什么 她挎了那么大个丑包
Why? Because she's brought a ludicrously capacious bag
里面到底装了什么啊
What's even in there?
挤地铁穿的平底鞋吗
Flat shoes for the subway?
还是她的饭盒啊 格雷格 太可怕了
Her lunch pail? Greg, it's monstrous.
硕大无比 可以带出去露营了
It's gargantuan. You could take it camping.
带着去抢银行都没问题
You could slide it across the floor after a bank job
随便你怎么说吧 反正她已经被我办了
Well, whatever. She's another tick on the chart.
恶心 兄弟
The Disgusting Brothers
别这么叫 咱们讽刺过度就伤人了 格雷格
Don't call us that. It was heavily iron ized, Greg
好吧 我只是开玩笑 我真的喜欢她
Okay. I'm kidding. I really do like her.
是吗 她把浴室里的装饰毛巾全用了
Well, she's used all the display towels in the bathroom
现在所有毛巾都湿哒哒的
and now they're sopping wet
她碟碟不休地谈论自己 还发到社交网络上
She's gab bling about herself and posting it on social media.
她询问别人隐私问题
She's asking people personal questions
她像饿了三天的疣猪一样 狂炫餐前开胃薄饼
and she's wolfing all the canapes like a famished warthog
那是大家过度反应了
People are overreacting.
她不过是跨了一个普通的包包
She brought a normal sort of handbag
你是文明社会里的笑柄
You are a laughingstock in polite society
你再也不能去看歌剧了,  -或许我们该走了
You'll never go to the opera again. -Maybe we should go
你没事吧 发生什么了
Are you okay? What happened?
没什么 我刚才 找洛根要自拍了
Nothing. I just asked Logan for a self ie.
你找洛根要自拍  -是啊
You asked Logan for a self ie? -Yeah.
我说 “恭喜你搞定了一笔大买卖”
I said " Congrats on the big deal'
然后说了声“进账啦” 有什么不对吗
I was like " K ar-ching", am I right?
就是跟他开个玩笑
I was being funny.
我跟她们的财务联系了
So I'm in touch with their bankers
南认为 她已经跟另一位买家口头约定好了
Nan thinks she's honor bound to another buyer
她拒绝了吗  -没有
Did she say no? -No
但她们已经快要接受交易的大纲了
But they're close to agreeing the outlines of a deal.
没多少人感兴趣 处理家事也是焦头烂额
There's not a ton of interest, managing the family's a nightmare
所以 她们想找一个优先竞标方来运营
so they're looking for a preferred bidder to run a bilateral.
她想今晚就确定这个优先竞标方
She wants to lock in that preferred bidder tonight
也就是说 她觉得这事不能成 但她也确实说了
So, she didn't think it could work. But she did say
她可以跟你聊聊小西
She could speak to you, Shiv.
好啊 那我要不要至少打个电话过去
Okay. Well, should I at least call?
确认下“灰色花园"的情况
Just check in at Grey Gardens
磨一磨南
and go, you know, mano a Nan-o?
看看有没有什么我们能做的
Just see if there's anything there at all?
发挥你的魔力吧
Work your magic.
还好吗 这里还不错吧
You good? It's nice, huh?
是啊 猪崽子们忙着吃东西
Yeah. Little piggies stuffing their mouths.
为什么所有人都他妈的这么开心
Why is everybody so fucking happy?
洛根...
Logan…
你没事吗  -当然
You okay? -Yeah
我在正确的时间谈成了那么大一笔交易
I got done a huge fucking deal in exactly the right time.
我有泛美网科 还有皮尔斯
I got A TN, plus Pierce.
还有大选 我手上全是筹码
I got the election. I got plenty on my plate
是啊
Sure.
这里好像有个牧师
I thought there might be a churchman.
你说什么
U h, I'm sorry?
我刚才听见有人提到红衣主教
A cardinal was mentioned. Bit of fucking class
杰瑞德怎么样
What about Jeryd?
门肯吗 他应该是想来的 但是
Mencken? I think that he hopes to, but realistically..
但是 他肯定是想来的 不过吉莉安在这
But I think that he hopes to. But Gillian is here.
好生热闹
Oh, who op-de-doop
你想让我跟孩子们联系吗
Do you want me to be in touch with the kids?
她什么时候打电话
When is she calling?
南吗 我猜她是想跟她那边所有人一起聊清楚
Nan, I think she just wants to talk to her whole gang
听着 我不会跟个龟孙的坐在这
Listen, I'm not gonna sit like a cunt.
巴巴地等着那个老太婆
waiting for that old crone.
风云人物
The man of the hour!
科林
Colin!
你没事吧  -没事 我们离开这里吧
-You all right? -Yeah. Let's get out of here.
是老爸 确认了
So it is Dad. Confirmed
对 这个女人真不简单哪
Yeah. Man, she's a complicated woman.
一副 “我跟别人说好了 我意已决
She's like, " I'm honor bound, my mind is made up.
不过 我们还要多久能谈谈”
" But also, how soon can we be there?"
去她的吧  -你怎么看
Fuck her! -What do you think?
我觉得 她恨老爸
I thinks he hates Dad
但也觉得 我们只是中看不中用的花架子
But also thinks we're fake fruit for display purposes only
我不知道
I don't know.
我们可以不管她了吗
Can we tell her to fuck off?
不要再跟老爸对着干了
Maybe not go back to the mat with Dad.
不要再回到那间房..
You know, back in that fucking room..
我们要不要摊牌  -什么意思
Shall we cards on the table? -Yeah
我真的很中意皮尔斯  -同意
-I do like Pierce. -Agreed
真他妈要命  -小罗 这很合理
-Fuck's sake! -Rome, it makes sense.
我们想要合作
We wanted to do something together
而我们懂新闻娱乐
and we know news, entertainment
这是现成就有的
and this is off the shelf.
所以 在这之前
So, I guess until now,
你就只是在耍我们吗
you've just sort of been stringing us along?
-不是  -另外 那玩意我也可以
-No. -I like the other shit, I do.
但我真的更满意这个
You know, I like this, I really do.
而且 其他一切都可能分崩离析
And besides, everything else might fall apart.
他有可能跑到711大开杀戒
He might go on a killing spree in 7-Eleven,
你的老二有可能卡在人工智能撸管机里
and you might get your dick stuck in an AI jerk machine.
我全得靠自己 因为没人会帮我
I have to look after myself because nobody else will
我喜欢这个提议
I like this.
那么 你要飞过去
So, you wanna fly there.
像 南·皮尔斯 参加温莎犬展的 小母狗一样吗
like Nan Pierce's little Windsor Dog Show bitch?
-只是去瞧瞧  -对
-It's just a checkout. -Yeah.
靠 真操蛋
Fuck! Shit!
我很担心
I'm worried, I guess
你想干老爸 你想干汤姆
Like you wanna fuck Dad. You wanna fuck Tom.
结果 只有我一个人想好好搞生意
I'm the only one who wants to set up a business as a business
而不是想干任何人
and doesn't wanna fuck anyone.
小罗 这次并购与老爸无关
Rome, this acquisition would be nothing to do with Dad
没半点关系  -我不信你
It's completely unrelated. -Don't believe you
真的  -我也是真的不信你
Seriously. -Seriously don't believe you.
好了 这不是为了报复老爸
Okay, well, this is not about getting back at Dad.
但 如果能让他难受 我觉得无伤大雅
but if it hurts him. It doesn't bother me.
我认为你不想这么做
I think that you don't wanna
是因为你害怕冲突
do this'cause you're scared of conflict.
说真的 小罗 理性点
Honestly, Rome, being rational.
先不谈家族内部矛盾
putting aside the internecine family concerns
以及个人的流言蜚语
the personal tittle tattle,
想想看 如果搞砸老爸几十年都为之疯狂的事
just think about how fucking funny it would be if we screw Dad
那有多好玩
over his decades-long obsession
你是个好人
You're a good guy.
谢谢 先生 你是我的朋友
-Thank you, sir. -You're my pal
谢谢
Thank you.
你是我最好的朋友  -谢谢
-You're my best pal. -Thank you.
我是说 人到底是什么
I mean, what are people?
是啊
Right.
究竟什么是人
What are people?
他们就是经济单位 我是巨人
They're economic units. I'm a hundred feet tall
他们都是侏儒
These people are pygmies.
但聚在一起 就形成了市场
But together, they form a market
好 没错
Okay. Right.
个人又是什么 他有价值和目标
What is a person? It has values and aims,
但在各种市场里运作
but it operates in a market
婚姻市场 工作市场
Marriage market, job market,
金钱市场 观点市场 等等
money market, market for ideas, et cetera.
所以 一切都是市场
So, everything is a market?
无论我做什么 都会遭人反对
Everything I try to do people turn against me
一切都和以前大不相同了 不是吗
Nothing tastes like it used to, does it?
早已物是人非了
Nothing is the same as it was.
你觉得 这一切结束后 还剩什么吗
You think there's anything after all this? Afterwards?
我不知道
I don't know.
我觉得没有了
I don't think so.
就是这样了 对吧
I think this is it, right?
或许吧
May be
我父亲非常虔诚
My Dad is very religious.
更实际一点呢
But realistically though?
我不知道  -就是这个答案
-I don't know. --And that's it.
我们不知道 我们无法知道
We don't know. We can't know.
但 我隐约有自己的想法
But I've got my suspicions.
我他妈隐隐约约有点想法
I've got my fucking suspicions.
瞧啊 等我一下
Lookie here! Pardon me!
你好哇 凯莉 今天一切都好吗
Hello, Kerry! And how are we today?
你能听到吗 信号有一点…
Hi! Can you hear me? The line is a little bit..
差不多吧 我们在中转 你能听见吗
Sort of. We're in transit. Can you hear me?
你让她把老爸的鸡巴从嘴里拿出来
You'd be able to hear her better
或许就能听得更清楚一点了
if she took Dad's cock out of her mouth.
什么
What's that?
我妹妹说 如果你把老爸的鸡巴从嘴里拿出来
That was my sister saying that we would hear you better
我们就能听得更清楚一点了
if you took Dad's cock out of your mouth
我的问题是 你们考虑打个电话给他吗
So. My question was, would you consider giving him a call?
我们会考虑 至少给他打个电话吗
Would we consider at least a call?
他是要道歉吗
Well, is he apologizing?
他有让我们打吗
Did he ask?
他…
He...
我觉得 他会想收到你们的消息
I know that he would love to hear from you
如果他打过来的话 我们就能知道了
If he were to call, then we would see.
从对他的了解来看 让他打电话得费不少劲
It's just gonna be a lot to get him to call, just knowing him
说实话 我们也很了解他
I think we know him pretty well, actually
但 我们从没舔过他的大乳头
We've never licked his big omelet nipples
我可以让他发短信要求打电话
I could get him to text a request for a call.
短信吗 我们还是想听到他的声音
Text? I'm afraid we're gonna need to hear that voice.
你可以把鸡巴塞回去了 我们要上飞机了
You can pop it back in your mouth. We're getting on the plane.
谢了 再见
Thanks, bye.
-混蛋  -出问题了
Dick. -Problem.
他不接我的电话 你打过去会接吗
He's not picking up for me. He pick up for you?
小威
Will. No
抱歉 能让我过一下吗
Excuse me, I'm sorry. Can I get through?
宝贝
Hey, baby!
听着 你知道婚礼的事
Listen. So, you know the wedding
我在想
I've been thinking..
好的 怎么
Okay, like...
在船上进行 够特别吗 头脑风暴一下…
Is the boat special enough? Like, brainstorming..
如果 我们在自由女神像下面结婚
What if we got married underneath the Statue of Liberty
再让铜管乐团伴奏
with a brass band?
找个说唱歌手 或者用喷气背包
Get a rapper. I don't know, jet packs
五彩纸屑 弹铁丝网
confetti guns, and razor wire
街头混战 促销大礼包
and bum fights, and, you know, goody bags
搞得光彩夺目一点  -街头混战吗
And hoopla and razzmatazz. -Bum fights?
老康 你听着精神错乱了 怎么回事
Con, you sound unhinged. What is this?
如果我能登上新闻报道
If I can get inserted into the news cycle
那就 省了一大笔 找媒体的钱
that's a huge savings from paid media
是吧
Right.
但婚礼..
The wedding.
我一直都... 听着很蠢 但我想要一个美好的婚礼
I've always... It's dumb, but I wanted a nice wedding
我很害怕 威拉
I'm scared, Willa
我他妈花了太多钱了 我开始害怕了
I have spent so much fucking money and it's getting scary
如果支持率跌破1% 我就成了笑柄
If I was to fall under 1%, I would become a laughing stock
你能考虑下吗 就稍微热闹一点
Would you just consider it? Just a little bit of hoopla?
只是为了最后助推一把
Just for the final push.
凯莉说 她知道他在哪了
Kerry said she knows where he is.
他现在回来了 你在笑什么
He's coming back now. What are you smiling for?
没什么
Nothing
怎么了
What?
恶心兄弟出门郊游
The Disgusting Brothers on motherfucking tour.
我们刚来了一发  -什么意思
We just did it. -What do you mean you did it?
她跟个爆竹一样 像酥脆花生酱
She's a firecracker, man. She's crunchy peanut butter.
等等 你打炮了 认真的吗 在哪打的
Wait. You did it? Are you serious? Where?
我们在找宝库 也就是雪茄保湿盒
We were looking for the armory slash-cigar-humidor
她把我拉进了客卧
and she pulled me into a guest bedroom
简直就是干柴烈火
and bingo-bongo hit that bango
你真的打炮了 格雷格.
You actually did it? Greg.
你完蛋了
You are fucked.
你完犊子了
洛根 他把监控武装到姥姥家了
Logan, he's camera'ed up the wazoo. CCTV
哪个房间  -所有房间 你知道的
-Which room? -Every room. You know that
我显然是不知道
I evidently did not know that
你说真的吗  -我当然说真的
-Are you serious? -Of course, I'm serious
他每晚 都会 边喝苏格兰威士忌 边回放录像
And he watches it back every night with a scotch
看看有没有人偷走黄油刀
See if anyone's stolen a butter knife.
他会把你直接做成虹尊刺身的
He's gonna fucking gut you like a rainbow trout.
操
Fuck!
所以 你做什么了 灯开着的吗
What did you do? Were the lights on?
跟我说实话 你真的做了吗
Did you actually do it? Tell me.
我们把手伸进对方的裤子里
We put our hands down each other's pants
翻找了一小会
And had a bit of a rummage
你们翻找出成果了吗
Did you rummage to fruition?
这一定要回答吗
Can I not say?
格雷格 你们意外地给他拍了部色情录像
You've accidentally made him a sex tape, Greg
天啊  -你得告诉他
Oh my God! -You need to tell him
好了 派对结束竞价了 走吧
Okay, party's over. Rival bid, let's go!
汤姆 格丽 卡尔 弗兰克 到楼上书房
Tom, Gerri, Karl, Frank, upstairs, library
把对手逼出来吧
Let's flush it out.
能稍等我一会儿吗
Would you mind just giving me a sec?
可以 当然
Okay. Sure.
你好
Hi!
你好呀
Hi
是这样的 她有点犹豫
So she's having a little wobble.
南吗 你什么意思
Nan? What do you mean?
她不确定跟你们见面好不好
She's not sure it feels right to meet you guys
她身体很不适
But she feels terrible.
好吧 所以 我们现在怎么办
Okay. So, what do we do?
她可能有点头疼
She might be getting a headache.
你们能不能 等她一会儿 看头疼会不会好
She wondered if you could give her five, see how it develops
行 当然
Okay, sure.
我们看看头疼会不会好吧
Let's see how the headache develops
行吧 老天爷
Okay, Jesus.
所以 谁从地缝里钻出来了
So, who's crawled out of the woodwork?
是谁
Who is it?
怎么了  -是孩子们 那群孩子正跟皮尔斯在一起
-What? -It's the Kids. The kids are with the Pierces.
竞争对手就是他们吗 奶奶个熊的
They are the rival bidders? Butter my be an pole.
他们怎么嗅到迹象的
How did they pick up the scent?
太多渠道了 所有人都知道他们在寻找收购者
A million ways. Everybody knows they're looking for suitors
他们能凑出钱吗
Could they even get the cash together?
洛根没法阻止他们吗
Couldn't Logan stop them?
如果韦斯达出售了
If Way star is sold.
他们有权 套现他们的百分之五股权
they have the right to liquidate their five percent s
也许你应该告诉他
You should probably tell him
不行 我专注于GoJo交易
Oh no. I'm very focused on the GoJo deal
这只是次要问题
This is really a side issue.
您真是值得信赖的顾问  -是的 但我要退出了
-You're such a trusted advisor. -Yeah, but I'm getting out
我不知道是什么消息 而且这超出我的权限了
I don't know what the news is, and it's beyond my purview
所以 我现在走开
and I'm walking away.
-小心糖尿病  -给我他妈的找出来
-Beware the blood sugar. -Well, fucking find out
先生 能跟您说句话吗  -什么 怎么了
-Sir, if I may have a moment. -What? What's the issue?
竞价者 也许是孩子们
The rival bidder, it's probably the kids
我认为 您没什么好担心的
I don't think you have anything to be concerned about
您才是不二之选
You are the solid option
汤姆 打给你老婆
Call your wife, Tom
打给你那不听话的老婆
Call your fucking wife
跟他们说 有本事自己出主意
and tell them to get their own fucking idea
真可悲
It's pathetic!
跟她说 她这辈子
And tell her she's never
从未自己出过任何一个主意
had a single fucking idea in her entire life!
什么事 没事 可以稍后再说
-What? -No, it can wait.
到底是啥
What else?
是私事 我能跟您私下聊吗
It's private. Can you and I just have a moment?
去那儿聊吧  -谢谢您 先生
Over there. -Thank you. Sir
你觉得她是不是在冷处理我们
You think she's just cooling us off?
玩儿老爸那招
Doing a Dad move?
不是的 小可怜头疼了
No, no. Poor thing has a headache
她现在感觉好些了
So, she's feeling a little better.
你们还想的话 她可以见见你们
If you like, she will see you.
好的 终于能和老太太聊聊报纸了
All right. Get to talk to an old lady about newspapers
太棒了 谢谢您
Amazing. Thank you so much
聊得怎么样
So how did it go?
他说 他觉得我无耻下流 令人作呕
So, he says he finds me disgusting and despicable,
但 他好像微笑了
but he kind of smiled
真的吗  -对
Did he? -Yeah.
你怎么说的
What did you say?
我说 她有点放荡
So, I said she's a bit wild
她很饥渴
She's quite eager
也许 她还飞了点叶子什么的
and may be she'd had a hit of the old wacky tabac ky or worse
还有 我从未想玷污他的府邸
And that I never intended to soil these halls
也许 她就是有点…
And maybe she's just a bit of a..
是个吸毒成瘾的爱屌女
Bit of a drug-addled, cock monster
所以 你全怪到她身上了
So, you blamed it on her.
你真有风度
You're so gallant.
她必须离开 懂吗
So, she's gonna have to leave, okay?
有这个必要吗
Is that really necessary?
你对此有意见吗  -不是 听我说
Do you have an issue with that? -No, look
科林 我喜欢她
Colin, I'm fond of her
但 我们每个人都按自己的意愿行事
but we must... each of us do as we see fit
她发在社交媒体了
She posted to social media.
我现在需要检查她的手机
I'm gonna have to ask to go through her phone
你想跟过来解释一下吗
You wanna come explain?
等等 抱歉 这样吧
Wait, sorry. You know what?
最好是你去尽你的责任
I think it is best if you go do what you have to do
我不想眼睁睁看着关塔那摩[监狱]的惨状
I don't wanna see what happens in Guantanamo.
你去吧 用你的方式 上帝会支持你的
So you go, do your ways, and God be willing
你们好 欢迎
Well, hello! Welcome!
很抱歉刚才的混乱 我的偏头痛太严重了
Apologies for the kerfuffle. I have an appalling migraine.
但我还能应对 最重要的是 你们怎么样
But I can manage. How are you all, more importantly?
-挺好的  -很高兴见到你
Great. -Great to see you.
这里很漂亮
And it's a lovely place.
看上去
It would seem that they
他们在肥料上花了很多钱
shred hundred-dollar notes for fertilizer.
所以 你们和父亲的关系 都还好吗
Now, how are you all fairing in terms of your father?
我们还行 就是 复杂的家事
We're fine. It's just a complicated, private situation
也就是 我们都恨他
Whereby we all hate him.
好吧 请坐
Well, please sit
听着 也许你们都知道了 我们在跟财务谈
Look, as you probably know, we are talking with our bankers
我们有很多
And we have a whole number
有趣的竞价可以考虑
of very interesting proposals to consider.
我觉得 已经可以收尾了
And I think it's all wrapped up.
所以 我想感谢你们的到来
So, I wanted to say thank you for coming
但 我觉得有一点迟了
but I think it's just a little bit too late
我们有优先竞标方了
We have a preferred bidder.
希望没给你们带来什么不便
I hope that I have not inconvenienced you
好吧 有趣的拜访 很高兴见到你们
Okay, well, lovely visit. Great to see you guys.
真的 我很抱歉
Really. I am very sorry
我能请你们喝两杯吗
May I offer you some bottles?
对我而言 它们也许只是果酱
They might as well be jars of jam to me.
但是 鉴赏家们还挺欣赏它们的
but the connoisseurs seem to like them.
忍怕 我是山猪 吃不来细糖
I fear I have peasant tastes.
你都不想听听我们的出价吗
You don't wanna just hear the offer?
19岁时 我就喜欢普通葡萄酒大卖场
I got a taste for hyper march e vin ordinaire
至今从未改变这个品味
when I was 19 years old and I have never been able to shake it.
我希望我的红酒是轻薄且酸的
I like my wine thin and vinegary.
就像她的男人们  -内奥米
Like her men. -Naomi!
不 但我真的担心这一切是徒劳的
No, but really I fear it is a trip made in vain.
另一个出价太好了
The other offer's just too good
长话短说 南 你之前对这个的看法是对的
Listen, long story short, Nan, you called this right before.
洛根想收购你的公司 然后搞砸它
Logan wants to take your company and fuck it.
他厌恶你
He loathes you
所以 他想收购你的财产 然后在泥里摩擦
and he wants to take your properties and roll them in the dirt.
我们不会这么做的
And we wouldn't do that
我觉得 这次总统大选之后
I think that after this election,
从国家角度而言 我们处于很糟糕的境地
we all, as a country, could be in a very bad place.
我们会保持您的价值观
We would maintain your values.
听上去都很好
That's all good and well
但 显然 出于这样或那样的原因
but obviously, with one thing and another,
我们都有责任
we have a responsibility
为我的家族和其他股东
to get the best possible deal for my family
获得最优交易
and the other shareholders
我相信我们在价格上有竞争力
I'm confident that we can be competitive on price.
杰米离婚 安在缅因的遭遇..
What with Jamie's divorce and Anne's disaster in Maine..
还有这个地方
And this place..
你们的财务状况如何 虽然我不太懂
How's your financing? Not that I understand at all
很稳健
It's robust.
泰勒斯和我们的团队可以跟你们详谈
Tellis and our team can talk to your people.
你们对未来如何打算
And in terms of your futures?
我们已经备好了辞呈
Well, we've written our resignation letters
与GoJo的协议将在48小时内签署
and the GoJo deal signs in 48 hours.
话虽如此 但你丈夫依然是泛美网科的主管
Nevertheless, you'd still be married to the head of ATN.
这有点麻烦  -我准备离婚了 所以…
That's a bit messy. -I'm getting a divorce, so.
天哪 好吧 为你感到遗憾
Oh.'Kay. I'm sorry to hear that
爱情消逝时 悲伤在所难免
Yes, it's a sad, sad day when love dies
听着 现在的情况有点复杂
Listen, this is very confusing
我不想谈报价 不是钱的问题
And I don't want to talk numbers. It's not about the numbers.
的确 的确
Totally. Totally
不妨由我们来报价吧
Shall we just say our number, though?
看看你们能不能接受
Just see if that makes any sense
我不喜欢这样
Oh, I don't like this.
让我觉得自己置身于一场竞价大战之中
Makes me feel like I'm in the middle of a bidding war.
可怕
Horrible.
不同的人报着不同的价格
Different people saying different numbers.
八十九十 接下来呢
Eight, nine. What's next?
我懂 也太令人困惑了 九十之后是什么啊 九十B吗
I know. It's so confusing. What comes after nine? Nine B?
听着 不介意我们内部沟通一下吧
Listen, would you mind if we all had a brief chat?
你们看过露台上的风景吗 美不胜收
Have you seen the view from the terrace? It's incredible.
独一无二  -好吧 我们去看看
Can't be at it. -All right. We'll try
谢谢你们
Thank you.
谢谢你 南
Thank you. Nan.
南还在考虑
Nan is thinking.
她希望 你能再给她一点时间
and she wondered if she could ask for your indulgence.
不是钱的问题
It's not a money question.
所以 你能迟点儿再跟她谈吗
So, you okay to hold on for a minute just before you talk to her?
我还能说什么  -好
Well, what else can I fucking say? -Okay
你好 是的 我们可以等
Hi. Yeah. We'll hold
现在都没人讲笑话了 是吗
Nobody tells jokes anymore, do they?
卡尔 你有什么笑话吗
Karl, do you have any jokes?
什么
What's that?
我说卡尔
I'm saying, Karl,
这里太压抑了
it's a bit dry in here.
你能讲个笑话吗
Do you have any jokes?
-让我想想  -压抑得快要窒息了 快讲吧
Well, let me think. -Dry as fucking dust. Come on!
骂我一顿 把我骂得狗血淋头
Roast me! Give me a drubbing
弗兰克 你先讲吧 幽默点
Frank, start. Be funny
我不擅长讲笑话 领导
It's not really my thing, Chief
你觉得我承受不了吗
You don't think I can take it?
这不是我的风格 我是说 要讲也行
No, it's just not my style. I mean, I can.
洛根·罗伊的问题是
The thing about Logan Roy is
洛根是把又老又硬的骨头
The thing about Logan is he's a tough old nut.
天哪 席德·凯撒[天才喜剧演员]在世 小格
Christ. Sid fucking Caesar. Greggy
你很刻薄 你是个刻薄的老头
You're mea n. You're a me an, old man.
刻薄的老混蛋 让所有人都过得心惊胆战
You're a mean, old bastard, and you scare the life out of folks.
这是你的特长 你现在就让我心惊胆战
That's your thing. You're scaring me right now
所以 我现在不知所措
And that's why I don't even know what to do
谁想闻闻 格雷格的手指
Who wants to smell Greg's finger?
猜猜是什么味道 赢的人得一块钱
Guess the scent, win a buck.
继续啊 挑战我
Come on! Roast me!
你的孩子们呢 你的孩子们呢 洛根叔公
Where are your kids? Where's all your kids, uncle Logan?
今天可是你的生日  -你老汉呢
On your big birthday. -Where's your old man?
你老汉呢 还在村野集市上吃男人鸡巴吗
Where's your old man? Still sucking cock at the county fair?
格丽 最近有收到什么有趣的图片吗
Gerri, been sent anything funny lately?
都是些不友善的信息 多谢 洛根
All a bit horrible for me. Thanks, Logan.
我没有不友善 我只是在开玩笑 真是奇怪一家人
I'm not being horrible, I'm being fun. Fucking Munsters
好的 很好 稍等
Okay, very good. Hang on
理论上 她希望 最晚今晚
So, she would like to get this figured out
就能最终敲定
in theory, at least, tonight
悬而不决 不是上策
The uncertainty is not good
他们想让我们今晚
They would like us to get our best foot forward
就报一个有诚意的指示性价格
on an indicative price tonight
没必要故作友善了 我该叫她滚蛋吗
No need to play nice. Should I tell her to fuck off?
洛根  -我在考虑
-Loge? -I'm thinking
她也在和他们谈吗  -我想是的
Is she talking to them? -I think so
好的 好的 凯莉 我需要一点意见
Okay, okay, okay. Kerry, I may need input
泰勒斯在吗
Tell is, you there?
是的 我想我们能凑齐
Hey, yeah. I think we can get that together
好 那我们就报价八十亿
Okay, so were gonna go in and say eight
起价八十亿
We're starting at eight.
如果真的有意向 就别这么强硬
But if we're going for this, let's not be hard asses
我们要让她知道有提价空间
We gotta let her know that we can see upside
但她得证明自己值得
but she's gotta help us prove it out.
好吧  -什么意思
-Okay. -Hello.
怎么了 是的 我很感兴趣 闭嘴
Yeah, what? Yes. I'm interested. Shut up
好 那我去跟她说..  -是的 她喜欢你
-Okay. So should I... -Yeah, she likes you.
八十亿可以  -谢谢 阿泰
Yeah, eight is good. -Thanks, T.
谢谢
Thanks.
是的 谢谢 你真棒  -好 回头联系
-Yeah, thanks. Top notch! -Great, call you back.
告诉她什么 我们错定七十亿吗
Tell her what? We anchor at seven?
没问题
Not a problem
好
Yeah.
不会太侮辱人吧
Not too insulting?
不 不会 确实有点侮辱人
No. It's fine. I mean, it's insulting
但不算伤感情
but it's not like you're
毕竟她对你没什么感情
wasting relationship capital. She hates you
从六十亿开始吧 但语气别太认真
Start at six. But like you're kidding around
七十亿比较稳妥 对吧
Seven is what we soft-floated, right?
先报六十亿吧 打击一下她的弱点
Six. Find something we've lost conviction on
让她知道
just to let her know that
我们不是天真无知的乡下人
we're not Terry fucking Turnip Truck over here
你好 南
Hi, Nan!
我很难开口 恐怕你也很难接受...
This may be hard to say for me and to tear for you..
谢谢
Thank you.
南 我们觉得...
Hi, Nan. So I think we're looking at.
我们有信心把价格开在八十亿
Were very relaxed about the eight billion landing spot
真不像话
This is disgusting
但 谢谢你们
But thank you.
我们需要一点时间  -好的
-We'l I just need a minute. -Okay.
好
Right.
他们不满意
They didn't love it.
你觉得他们出了多少
What are they up to, do you think?
我不知道  -我不想失去这买卖 汤米
-I don't know. -I don't wanna lose this, Tommy
你想直接提高价格吗 到多少
You wanna just jump right up? What to?
打给你老婆 打给小西
Call your wife. Call Shiv.
她很欣赏八十亿的报价
So, she appreciates eight
是吗 她很欣赏吗 很好
Yeah? She appreciates it? Cool.
但 她想知道 是否还有小小的提价空间
But she wonders if there's a little more upside.
好
Okay
阿泰
Telly.
喂
Hello.
八十五亿 我们的...资金够吗 阿泰
Eight-five. Can we... can we go there, T?
我不知道 财团的 确切组成
Well, I... I don't have the precise composition
和即期汇票金额
of our consortium and, obviously, DD
但 我了解对方的价值 我觉得我们可以
But I know the asset and I think we can get there.
你在对看游艇目录打手枪吗 阿泰
You fucking jerking it to your yacht catalogue there, T?
伙计们 这太激动人心了
This is exciting, guys!
谢谢你 泰勒斯 你的建议不错
Thanks, Tell is. That's a great insight.
他要收我们两亿美元的战略咨询费
He's gonna bill us 200 mil for that strategy advice.
有电话进来
Incoming.
喂 汤姆
Hello? Tom?
好 他想跟我们聊聊
Okay. He wants a discussion
怎么 爸让汤姆来跟进吗 科林不在吗
What? Dad's-got To m on this? What? Was Colin not available?
-小西 -去你的 山人
-Hey, Shiv. -Fuck you, man mountain!
听着 我们想确认一下
Hey! So look, we were just wondering
自己是不是被耍了 因为目前都只是指示性报价
if we're not being played a little here since this is all indicative.
好吧 他报价多少 汤姆
Okay, What did he go up to, Tom?
我不能告诉你  -说吧汤姆 你能告诉我
-I can't tell you that. -Come on, Tom, you can tell me.
他报了九十亿吗 没有 对吧
Did he go to nine? He didn't go to nine, did he?
我们在想 同等条件下
We were just wondering, you know, all things being equal
资产的价值是固定的
the asset does have a price
没有必要为了怄气而加价
and it would be crazy to add an emotional premium here
我们要不要找找关系
So should we be looking for a back door.on this?
爸的上限是多少?
What's Dad's ceiling?
你们的上限是多少
Well, what's your ceiling?
你先说 汤米 互信共赢 兄弟
You go first, Tommy. Build that trust, br uh.
他的上限是…
His ceiling is..
你爸...
Your dad is just.
我不能说…
I can't say...
小西 我们能谈谈吗
Shiv, could we just talk?
我们的上限是一百二十亿  -别扯啦
-Our ceiling is 12. -Fuck off!
-真的  -好吧 当然
-Yeah. -Okay, sure.
我们的也是 挂了
Ours, too. Okay
我觉得 爸可能会冲九 九十五
I think Dad is gonna go to nine. 9,5
所以 我们需要出九十五 能行吗 泰利斯
So we need to be at 9,5. Right, Tell is?
那个啥 我在想…
You know what, I wonder..
我在想 咱们要不别扣扣搜搜了 直接喊一百吧
I wonder if we don't nickel and dime it and we just go to ten.
我们认为 爸会喊八十五或九十
So, we think Dad's at eight-five, nine.
所以 我们出九十五 压死他们
So, we go nine-five to top them out.
但是一百 只是为了表明我们很认真吗
But ten? Just to show that were really serious?
只不过是多了五亿
That's just an extra half bil?
这是决胜点 我们会直接拿下
It's definitive. It ends the conversation.
就算是为了拿下它 也是一个很大的数目
Well, that's a pretty penny for a conversation ender
我就不能在她的破保险杠里爽一下吗
Can't I just, like, jizz in her Break Bumper?
我们能圆满拿下
It rounds it out
是 能圆满拿下
Oh, it rounds it out, yeah
确实可以 这个数字拉开了不少差距
It does that, it makes it extremely divisible.
你们应该知道 5亿美元是多少吧
I mean, you do know what half a billion dollars is, right?
等于500个一百万美元
500 million dollars?
当然知道  -泰勒斯
-Yeah. -Tell is...
100万美元等于1000个一千美元 你们都知道吧
A million is a thousand thousand. You do know that.
500倍的1000个一千美元现钱
500 times a thousand thousand of actual money
我们大可以花在雪地摩托和寿司上
that we could be spending on snowmobiles and sushi.
确实是我们的极限
It's getting top py.
但是 如果能成为首选竞标者 就太值了
but it would be great to be the preferred bidder here.
但 这真的值得吗
But is it actually worth it?
我觉得 标主就会开出这个价
It's worth what the top bidder will pay, I guess.
我真希望我也像你一样 读过哈佛商学院 阿泰
I really wish I went to Harvard Business School like you, T.
和像你这样的智力巨人谈话
It is intimidating talking to an intellectual giant
令人生畏
like yourself.
百吗 -百
Ten? -Ten.
我是说
I mean...
好吧 行 一百就一百 去他的吧
Okay. Yeah, ten. Fuck you. Ten.
所以 南 听着
So. Nan, look.
我们喜欢你们公司 和你们的传统
We love the company and the heritage.
我们想提出一个 我们认为能够体现公司价值的报价
and we'd like to make an offer that we think values the company
结束这场商谈 画下句点
and ends the conversation and closes this out.
象征性地与你们握握手
On an indicative handshake
我们希望带领皮尔斯集团步入下一个辉煌
we'd like to take Pierce to the next stage
我们出价一百亿美元
of its evolution with a bid of ten billion dollars
这给了我们很多思考的余地
That gives us something to think about.
她们不再接受其他竞标者出价了
So they're not accepting another bidder
你说什么
Excuse me?
她们说 她们已经接受了足以结束商谈的报价
They said they've received a conversation-ending offer
告诉她们 我会往上加  -她说 她们很满意目前的报价
Tell the m I'll go up. -She says they're content
简直放屁
That's bullshit.
她们给我的印象 像是九十五以上
I get the impression it's upwards of 9,5
他们可真天才 一百亿吗
Fucking geniuses. Ten?
我感觉像是一百亿
I get a ten feeling.
感觉我们应该开点香槟庆祝庆祝
Kind of feels like we should fucking open some champagne.
我要回洛杉矶 回到我的卧室
I am going back to LA to retire to my bedroom
非常粗暴地 让自己爽一把
and pull myself off quite aggressively hard
非常感谢你的邀约
Thankyou very much.
副驾是我的  -等下
Shotgun. -Hang on!
你能给我开免提吗 小西  -好啊 是汤姆
Will you speakerphone me, Shiv? -Yeah. It's Tom
大家好
Hi! Okay.
你们爸也在 他有个口信
So, I have your dad and he has a message
恭喜你们 说出了最大的数字 一群他妈的白痴
Congratulations on saying the biggest number, you fucking morons
我们应该气到他了
I think we got him.
是啊
Yeah.
是我
It's me.
蒙代尔...
Mondale...
没事的
It's okay.
回来了
Hey.
抱歉 我吵醒你了吗
Sorry, did I wake you?
没有 我以为你要住酒店
No. I thought you were hotel ing.
就是回来换几件衣服
I needed wardrobe access, actually
我以为 你已经把你最喜欢的 都拿走了
I thought you took your favorites.
我不想局限于我最喜欢的那几件 汤姆
I don't wanna be restricted to my favorites, Tom
好吧 你想谈谈吗
Okay. Do you wanna talk?
我听说 你和格雷格 现在自称“恶心兄弟“了
I hear you and Greg call yourselves the Disgusting Brothers now.
是的
Right.
很酷哦
Pretty cool.
你们有商标吗 有制定"戒训“吗
Do you have a logo, and do you do " The Rules "?
格雷格是你的僚机吗
Is Greg your wingman?
我和内奥米只是偶尔出去喝一杯小西
We sometimes grab a drink, Shiv.
真酷 我听说你现在开始跟模特约会了
It's pretty cool. I hear you date models now.
我们同意彼此在冷静思考的时候
Well, we agreed that we could have a look around
骑驴找马 不是吗
while we had a think, right?
你状态不错 五迷三道的
You look good. Ripped
我不这么觉得 但 还是谢谢你
Well, I don't think so. But thank you
汤姆 你对模特很感兴趣吗
Did you get buff for the models, Tom?
你会把她们带回来 尝试各种姿势吗
Do you bring them back here and do the positions?
汤姆 你现在会和你的模特尝试各种姿势吗
Do you do all the positions with your models now, Tom?
你和格雷格是轮流来的吗
Do you take turns with Greg?
她们会坐在你脸上 让你闭嘴吗
Do they sit on your face to shut you up?
你真的想无情地揭开
Do you really want to get into a full accounting
我们的婚姻里的痛点吗
of all the pain in our marriage?
因为 如果你想 我也可以
Cause if you do, I can do that
蒙代尔怎么样
How's Mondale?
它很好 你不用太担心
Mondale's fine. Don't worry about Mondale
我猜它不怎么认得出你的气味了
I guess he doesn't recognize your scent any longer.
事情变得复杂了
Well, things have become complicated
我想知道 真的有办法解决吗
I wonder if there's even a way through this
是的
Right.
我想知道 咱们是不是可能已经无路可走了
You know, I wonder if we might've run out of road
我们不是打算大谈一场吗
We were going to have a big talk
我想知道 你是不是想正式地.. 你懂吗
I wonder if you might want to make it official, you know?
你想谈谈吗
Do you wanna talk?
有一些事情 我不介意说出来 解释一下
There's some things I wouldn't mind saying and explaining
我不想费劲 一通扯皮 还什么都捞不着 汤姆
I don't wanna rake up a whole lot of bullshit for no profit, Tom.
但我感觉  -别说了
But I feel... -Just stop!
我觉得 听你说这些 对我没好处
I don't think it's good for me to hear all that.
我想 你和我 可能是时候翻篇了
I think it might be time for you and I to move on
这话让我很难过
That makes me sad.
当然了
Sure.
你真的不想谈谈发生的事情吗
And you don't want to talk about what happened?
汤姆 我们可以谈事谈到死
Tom, I think we could talk things to death
但 实际上 我们都只是犯了一些错误
But actually, we both just made some mistakes.
我认为抱头痛哭
I think a whole lot of crying
和扯一大堆废话 是没屌用的
and bullshit is not gonna help that
如果你没意见
If you're good,
我们就可以昂首阔步的分别
we can just walk away with our heads held high
并 祝对方好运 你说是吗
and say good luck, yeah?
那 好吧
Well, okay
我可以试试和你再做一次爱
I could see if I can make love to you.
你想做吗
Would you like to?
我不是很想 汤姆
I don't think so, Tom
我应该离开吗, 还是说 你要走
Should I go? Or are you gonna go?
我很累 所以..
I'm tired, so..
但你可以留下 如果你想的话
But you can stay there, if you like
好的
Okay.
这就是咱俩的结局了吗
So this is it?
是的 我想是的
Yeah, I guess
走出这一步了...
Gave it a go...
是的 我们走出这一步了
Yeah, we gave it a go.
两名男子因争吵过度而受伤
Two men sustained life-threatening injuries
其至有生命危险
as result of a brawl gone too far
然而 在这个为期三天的家庭友好活动中 没有动过真格
However, no shots were fired at this family friendly 3-day event
相反的 是布莱恩·艾伦和皮特·梅耶斯
Instead, Brian Allen and Pete Meyers
这两位枪械专家 凭借自身的资质..
two firearms experts in their own right.
喂 洛根
Hello? Logan?
希德 我刚刚看了“此刻焦点”
Cyd, I just watched the top of the hour.
全是胡扯
It's bullshit.
大家晚上真的要看的
People watch ATNight,
我晚上也要看的
I watch AT Night.
我知道了
Okay.
这个臭傻逼又是哪位
Who is this fucking lunk anyway?
他看起来像一颗戴着假发的蛋蛋
He looks like a ball sack in a toupee.
你没戏唱了吗 希德
Are you losing it, Cyd?
我正在尽全力处理 洛根
I'm all over it, Loge
你他妈的没戏唱了吗
Are you fucking losing it?
我去处理 别担心
I'm on it. Don't worry
此事件已经玷污了一个以家庭为核心的
" This has sullied a family-oriented
完全和平的场合
and entirely peaceful occasion."
费耶特维尔枪展 仍将开放
The Fayetteville Gun Show continues.
我们会在这之后马上回来
We'll be back right after this